// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Total number of continents in the World is____?",
    answer: "7",
    options: [
      "5",
      "7",
      "6",
      "10"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which one is the largest ocean in the World?",
    answer: "Pacific",
    options: [
      "Pacific",
      "Indian",
      "Arctic",
      "Atlantic"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Total number of oceans in the World is____?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "6",
      "5",
      "9",
      "8"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which country gifted the 'Statue of Liberty' to USA in 1886?",
    answer: "Frence",
    options: [
      "Frence",
      "England",
      "Brazil",
      "Canada"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Dead Sea is located between which two countries?",
    answer: "Jordan and Israel",
    options: [
      "Turkey and UAE",
      "Jordan and Sudan",
      "Jordan and Israel",
      "UAE and Egypt"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "In which ocean 'Bermuda Triangle' region is located?",
    answer: "Atlantic",
    options: [
      "Pacific",
      "Indian",
      "Arctic",
      "Atlantic"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which country is also known as 'Land of the Midnight Sun'?",
    answer: "Norway",
    options: [
      "Iceland",
      "Greenland",
      "Ireland",
      "Norway"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which country is also known as the 'Land of Rising Sun'?",
    answer: "Japan",
    options: [
      "New Zealand",
      "China",
      "Japan",
      "UAE"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In which country, white elephant is found?",
    answer: "Thailand",
    options: [
      "Thailand",
      "Sri Lanka",
      "India",
      "Malaysia"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which one is the largest producer of tea in the World?",
    answer: "China",
    options: [
      "China",
      "India",
      "Kenya",
      "Sri Lanka"
    ]
  },


  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];